Professor Melhase decided to take a trip to Germany via Raesfeld airport. 
She then rented a BMW and drove it to Berlin. 
On her way, she passed a Baeckerei and decided to stop. 
She then felt hungry and ate a Bratwurst.
After a stroll down the Hauptstrasse, she felt that she needed a Gebaeck as well.
On her way, she saw a nice Porshe on the road.
It was parked outside of a Biergarten.
She then decided to buy a Dirndl for tonights plans at the Ratskeller.
Once she arrived, she noticed Rammstein was performing as the evenings scheduled entertainment.
Ironically, she was able to have a conversation with Rammstein about her planned visit to a nearby Schloss while they enjoyed an Apfelkuchen.
Ironically, she was able to have a conversation with Rammstein about her planned visit to a nearby Schloss while they enjoyed an Apfelkuchen.
